<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Staking on CyberMiles News and Articles</title>
    <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/tags/staking/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Staking on CyberMiles News and Articles</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 May 2020 15:01:23 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://blog.cybermiles.io/tags/staking/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>OKEx Pool as CyberMiles&#39; Validator: Stake and win a Cube</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/2020-05-28-okex-pool-staking-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 May 2020 15:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/2020-05-28-okex-pool-staking-en/</guid>
      <description>OKEx Pool became one of CyberMiles’ validator and is currently ranking the third with 27238182 voting powers and declared a compensation rate of 30 percent.
OKEx Pool is a world’s leading comprehensive mining pool built upon the world’s leading cryptocurrency exchange OKEx, offering a one-stop mining and trading experience for users, supporting the mining of PoW, PoS, and PoS-variant cryptocurrencies. It has become supernodes of multiple cryptocurrencies, including EOS and COSMOS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OKEx 矿池当选CyberMiles 超级节点</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/2020-05-28-okex-pool-staking/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 May 2020 15:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/2020-05-28-okex-pool-staking/</guid>
      <description>OKEx 矿池当选 CyberMiles 超级节点，目前以总投票权27238182，排名第三，报酬比率为30%。 OKEx 矿池是全球领先的综合性矿池，依托数字资产交易平台OKEx</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TISS by TokenInsight Becomes CyberMiles Latest Validator and Startegic Partner</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190902-cybermiles-staking-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2019 15:00:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190902-cybermiles-staking-en/</guid>
      <description>CyberMiles is excited to announce a new #Validator, TISS by TokenInsight, a leading blockchain rating, research and analytics agency.
TISS&#39;s validator compensation rate is initially set at a low 25% to encourage stakes from the CMT community.
TokenInsight Staking Service (TISS) has officially entered a strategic partnership with CyberMiles, with a focus on data collaboration, community governance, and ecosystem development.
Building on its CyberMiles collaboration, TISS is slated to run validator nodes for multiple PoS blockchains, joining in the effort to secure and grow the PoS ecosystem.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CyberMiles App Releases its Newest Version, Enabling Staking Function</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190625-cmt-staking-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2019 15:30:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190625-cmt-staking-en/</guid>
      <description>CyberMiles App (formerly CMT Wallet)3.0 is officially launched, and the mobile App staking CMT function is now enabled! Now users can use the CyberMiles App to stake their CMTs to validators (supernodes) to get block revenue. Come and download here!
Based on the current stake of the whole network, now that the stake 10,000 CMT, the compensation rate is 30%, the block income that can be obtained in one year is 1515 CMTs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CMT 手机权益投票已经上线，快来获取区块奖励吧</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190625-cmt-staking-zh/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2019 15:00:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190625-cmt-staking-zh/</guid>
      <description>CyberMiles APP（原CMT Wallet）3.0 正式上线，手机APP权益投票CMT功能上线了！现在用户可以使用CyberMiles APP 将CMT 权益投票给</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to stake with CyberMiles App to get Block Award</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190625-cmt-staking-tutorial-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2019 15:00:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190625-cmt-staking-tutorial-en/</guid>
      <description>CyberMiles App (formerly CMT Wallet) 3.0 enables staking function today!!! Hooray! Now CMT holders can get block award by staking with mobile App!
After the mainnet upgrade, the main factors for block award calculation are:
  Total staked amount in the whole CyberMiles network.
  The validator’s compensation rate. The lower the remuneration rate, the better for the staker (delegator).
  Your staked CMT amount. the higher the amount, the higher the block award.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>如何使用CyberMiles APP 进行权益投票，获取区块奖励</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190625-cmt-staking-tutorial-zh/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2019 15:00:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190625-cmt-staking-tutorial-zh/</guid>
      <description>CyberMiles APP（原CMT Wallet）已经开通权益投票功能，现在CMT 持有者可以通过手机APP获得区块奖励收入啦！ 经过主链升级后，现在区块奖励的主</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CyberMiles 公链新上线超级节点SNZ Holding</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190618-cmts-staking-zh/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2019 15:30:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190618-cmts-staking-zh/</guid>
      <description>CyberMiles 公链新上线了超级节点SNZ Holding。SNZ Holding 将自我权益投票300万CMT，报酬比率为25%。 SNZ Holding致力于提供专业的POS矿</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Today CyberMiles Blockchain Welcomes Another Validator, SNZ Holding</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190618-cmts-staking-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2019 15:30:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190618-cmts-staking-en/</guid>
      <description>CyberMiles community embraces a newcomer Validator today! SNZ Holding, CyberMiles&amp;rsquo; newest Validator, is up and running, joining in the maintainance of the network security of CyberMiles blockchain.
To be a Validator, SNZ Holding has self-staked 3 million CMTs as a commitment to CMT Community. It claims a compensation rate of 25% for all its delegators.
SNZ Holding is an institution dedicated to providing high-standard and professional POS validation services. SNZ has been engaged in investment, consultancy, community building and other business related to blockchain since 2016 and is an early investor in Ethereum, Dfinity, Cosmos, Polkadot and other renowned projects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ask CyberMiles Question 3: Is it easy to build DApps on Cybermiles blockchain and what background knowledge do I need?</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190509-amaq3-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2019 16:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190509-amaq3-en/</guid>
      <description>Q: Is it easy to build DApps on Cybermiles blockchain and what background knowledge do I need?
A: It is easy. For the traditional software developers, there are two things to learn.
The first is a programming language called Lity, based on Solidity from Ethereum, with the same grammar but with slightly different keywords. [Lity] develops smart contracts, and then you use a Javascript library called web3 to interact with the smart contracts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ask CyberMiles Question 2: Is there any chance for staking community to get a simple calculator for staked CMTs?</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190509-amaq2-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2019 12:06:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190509-amaq2-en/</guid>
      <description>Q: Is there any chance for staking community to get a simple calculator for staked CMTs?
A: Yes. We have simplified computation. ROI depends on 2 factors: the amount of CMTs put on stake; the ratio of CMTs between cube and Wallet.
There will be a simple calculator on CMT explorer to show real time ROI. Caculator comes with the new version of CMT Wallet.
Learn more at cybermiles.io.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>