<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blockchain on CyberMiles News and Articles</title>
    <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/tags/blockchain/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blockchain on CyberMiles News and Articles</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 10:01:23 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://blog.cybermiles.io/tags/blockchain/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>CyberMiles App User Guide</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20211013-tutorial-v2.0-01-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 10:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20211013-tutorial-v2.0-01-en/</guid>
      <description>CyberMiles Foundation recommends that users withdraw their tokens from the exchanges to their own decentralized cryptocurrency wallets, and keep them safe.
Cryptocurrency asset is stored with a public address coupled with a private key. Whoever gets the private key will be the owner. If users keep the private key themselves, there might be the risk of forgetting or losing the private key. With CyberMiles app you can store your CMT securely and only need to remember a password you set.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CyberPay Payment User Guide</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20211013-tutorial-v2.0-03-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 10:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20211013-tutorial-v2.0-03-en/</guid>
      <description>CyberPay is the payment service of CyberWorld NFT marketplace. USDT can be exchanged 1:1 with Diamond and exchanged back. We will allow the purchase of Diamond with a credit card (USD) soon.
Note: Diamond (shortened as DO) is a stable cryptocurrency issued by CyberWorld and pegged to USD to allow users to trade NFT on CyberWorld. 1 Diamond = 1 USD = 1 USDT. This guide will talk about 1：How to use USDT to exchange for Diamond 2: How to use Diamond to exchange for USDT</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CyberWorld on the Mobile-User Guide</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20211013-tutorial-v2.0-02-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 10:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20211013-tutorial-v2.0-02-en/</guid>
      <description>CyberWorld is an NFT marketplace built and operated by CyberMiles together with Sino-global. It can be used to collect and trade truly rare digital art. Each art piece is created by an artist and NFTized with blockchain technology. It will be a crypto digital platform that serves the content creators and their supporters the best.
CyberWorld has Web and mobile versions. This is the user guide for the Mobile version. The guide will explain: 1: How to create an NFT collection 2：How to min an NFT 3：How to transfer my NFT 4：How to sell my NFT 5：How to buy a fixed priced NFT 6：How to offer to buy NFT at a certain price.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CyberMilesNFT Newsletter - CyberWorld NFT Marketplace V2.0 to be Launched</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20210927-nft-news13-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 10:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20210927-nft-news13-en/</guid>
      <description>Finally! CyberWorld V2.0 will be launched in a few days. The CyberWorld engineering and product team has updated the operation staff on this great news, so we are here to announce it to CyberWorld supporters with all the excitement.
First of all, we’d like to thank all supporters for your patience waiting for such a long time after the launch of V1.0 several months ago. CyberWorld NFT marketplace will be worth the wait.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CyberMilesNFT Newsletter- How CyberWorld Empowers Content Creators on Patreon and more? </title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20210916-nft-news12-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2021 10:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20210916-nft-news12-en/</guid>
      <description>Patreon is more than a crowdfunding platform Patreon was founded by Jack Conte and Sam Yam in 2013. Creators can sell their content or works directly to their fans on Patreon. In addition, subscribers can donate a certain amount of money to the creators and artists they support to help them grow.
Patreon is a membership-based platform that allows creators to monetize on their creations. The starting point is to provide ongoing funding for creators and artists: they can &amp;ldquo;ask&amp;rdquo; fans for money if their works are uploaded.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CyberMilesNFT 简讯－CyberWorld 如何赋能 Patreon 和其它平台的内容创作者？</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20210916-nft-news12-zh/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2021 10:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20210916-nft-news12-zh/</guid>
      <description>Patreon 不止是一个众筹平台 Patreon 艺术家平台是由 Jack Conte 和 Sam Yam 于2013年创立的。不同的内容创作者，如画家、音乐创作者、文章作者，甚至程序员，可以在 Patreon 上向粉</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CyberMilesNFT Newsletter - Calling for Creators to Make NFTs on CyberWorld </title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20210903-nft-news11-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 10:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20210903-nft-news11-en/</guid>
      <description>CyberWorld NFT Marketplace will allow credit card payment in November. In addition, CyberWorld will provide the NFT airdrop distribution tool, which helps artists and content creators to produce many NFTs at one time and airdrop them to their followers and fans. Wanna have a try and mint an NFT and transfer it to your fans, family, and friends? Join CyberWorld now to enjoy creator perks!
Background About CyberWorld and the Team: CyberWorld is a blockchain NFT marketplace jointly built by CyberMiles and Sino-Global Shipping America, Ltd.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CyberMilesNFT 简讯- CyberWorld 招募内容创作者入驻，生成 NFT</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20210903-nft-new11-zh/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 10:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20210903-nft-new11-zh/</guid>
      <description>CyberWorld NFT 交易平台将在十月前上线法币兑换功能，消费者可以使用信用卡购买 NFT； 对于艺术家或各种形式的内容创作者来说，CyberWorld 将提供服务</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Market Research (Reference: TokenInsight)</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20210823-nft-news10-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2021 10:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20210823-nft-news10-en/</guid>
      <description>Background： Thanks to TokenInsight for its detailed report on the NFT market in Q2 and July. According to TokenInsight 2021 Q2 &amp;amp; July NFT Industry Report, we make a conclusion with the report about the hottest projects, developments, and latest data on the NFT market. TokenInsight is a great partner of CyberMiles and a supportive validator on the CM public blockchain. Welcome to stake with them. Here is the tutorial: How to stake with CyberMiles App to get Block Award.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>市场调研（数据来源：TokenInsight）</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20210823-nft-new10-zh/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2021 10:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20210823-nft-new10-zh/</guid>
      <description>背景： 首先感谢 TokenInsight 对 NFT 市场第二季度以及7月的动态做了详细的行业报告，这份调研主要根据 TokenInsight 的行业报告进行分析和总结。TokenInsight 是 CyberMiles 的</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CyberMilesNFT Newsletter - CyberWorld Supports BOA in Building Their NFT Marketplace</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20210818-nft-news9-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 10:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20210818-nft-news9-en/</guid>
      <description>With the heat of NFT continues to rise, all industries are jumping on the NFT bandwagon. CyberWorld partnered with the Bank of Asia (BOA) in building their BOA’s NFT marketplace, BOAX, in July 2021. With the grand opening of the 2021 Olympic Games, BOA Financial Group officially launched the new premium NFT marketplace BOAX, which allows users to trade digital assets online. The first NFT artwork, “Olympic Happiness,” exclusive was released on the BOAX NFT Marketplace on 23 July 2021, which was created by Dr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CyberMilesNFT 简讯－CyberWorld 支持合作伙伴 BOA 建立其首个 NFT 交易平台</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20210818-nft-news9-zh/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 10:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20210818-nft-news9-zh/</guid>
      <description>随着 NFT 的热度持续攀升，各行各业争先恐后的加入了 NFT 的热潮。今年七月，CyberWorld 与亚洲银行（BOA）建立合作伙伴关系，全力支持 BOA 建立其</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CyberMilesNFT Newsletter - NFT Market’s Regulatory Challenges</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20210813-nft-news8-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Aug 2021 10:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20210813-nft-news8-en/</guid>
      <description>In the previous CyberMiles Newsletter series article analyzing the challenges of hype, money laundering, illegal financing, infringement, and fraud that the NFT market faces in detail, we pre-announced discussion on the regulation of the NFT market. NFT market has to be regulated to protect all parties involved, not only those who simply want to buy the NFTs for collections but also the owners of artworks and artists who want to release NFTs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CyberMilesNFT 简讯－NFT 市场面临的监管挑战</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20210813-nft-news8-zh/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Aug 2021 10:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20210813-nft-news8-zh/</guid>
      <description>在之前的 CyberMilesNFT 的系列文章中，我们对 NFT 市场所面对的包括炒作、洗钱、非法融资、侵权和欺诈在内的的困境进行了详细的分析，并提前预告了之后会发布一篇 NFT 市</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CyberMilesNFT Newsletter - Under the Boom of Digital Collectibles, What the Challenges NFT Faces?</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20210806-nft-news7-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2021 10:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20210806-nft-news7-en/</guid>
      <description>Last week, CyberMiles shared an article about the pros and cons of OpeaSea and CyberWorld (Click here for more details). Today, we&#39;ll talk about some issues of the NFT market.
As mentioned in the previous CyberMiles articles, NFT speared ahead in the arts, sports, games, music, fashion, and other industries. NFT is continues expanding its presence. Digital art is moving from the niche to the masses. There is no doubt that NFT has led to the emergence of new forms of digital work transactions and marketplaces, providing high-profile and underground artists with a new way of income.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CyberMilesNFT Newsletter — What Are the Advantages of CyberWorld comparing with OpenSea?</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20210802-nft-new6-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Aug 2021 10:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20210802-nft-new6-en/</guid>
      <description>With the rise of the NFT market, led by some notable projects like NBA Topshop, CyrproPunks, the NFT market has seen a wave of digital collectibles and NFT exchange platforms. Devin Finzer launched an NFT exchange platform in 2017 called &amp;lsquo;OpenSea&amp;rsquo;, attracting a lot of attention as an early NFT project platform. As a result, the total market sales grew from $8 million in January to $150 million in March 2021.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CyberMilesNFT 简讯 - 和 OpenSea 相比，CyberWorld的优势在哪儿？</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20210802-nft-new6-zh/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Aug 2021 10:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20210802-nft-new6-zh/</guid>
      <description>随着 NFT 市场的兴起，由 NBA Topshot、CryproPunks 等项目引领的 NFT 市场带动了一波数字收藏品、NFT 交易平台的诞生。Devin Finzer 在20</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CyberMilesNFT 简讯 - 数字收藏品热潮下 NFT 面临的问题</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20210806-nft-news7-zh/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Aug 2021 10:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20210806-nft-news7-zh/</guid>
      <description>上周，CyberMiles 分享了关于 OpenSea 与 CyberWorld 的优缺点的文章（还没阅读的小伙伴可点击此处查看哦），今天我们就来聊一聊无论是 OpenSea 还是 CyberWorld 面对的 NFT 市场存</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CyberMilesNFT Newsletter- The NFT Boom: Luxury Brands Lead the Digital Fashion Trend?</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20210720-nft-new5-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jul 2021 10:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20210720-nft-new5-en/</guid>
      <description>The age of digital consumption seems to be changing the marketing model of every industry. Fashion brands seem to transfer to digital networks and technology as a way out of their transformation and upgrading. The luxury group LVMH formed a partnership with Google in June that will use AI to provide personalized services and content in order to enhance user experience. LVMH, Cartier’s parent company Richemont and Prada jointly announced that the three parties plan to create a solution powered by &amp;lsquo;Aura Blockchain&amp;rsquo;, a global luxury blockchain open to all luxury brands.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CyberMilesNFT 简讯- NFT 热潮下：奢侈品牌引领数字时尚</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20210720-nft-news5-zh/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jul 2021 10:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20210720-nft-news5-zh/</guid>
      <description>数字消费时代似乎在改变着各行各业的营销模式。时装品牌似乎也转向数字网络与技术作为自己转型的出路。奢侈品集团 LVMH 在6月与谷歌建立合作伙伴关系，将</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>