<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>en on CyberMiles News and Articles</title>
    <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/categories/en/</link>
    <description>Recent content in en on CyberMiles News and Articles</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Aug 2021 10:01:23 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://blog.cybermiles.io/categories/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Roadmap 2021 for CyberMiles NFT Platform CyberWorld</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20210810-cyberworld-roadmap-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Aug 2021 10:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20210810-cyberworld-roadmap-en/</guid>
      <description>CyberMiles NFT Platform, CyberWorld, has been officially launched together with Sino Global in May 2021 ahead of schedule.
CyberWorld Version 0.5 attracted great attention from over 120, 000 users in the community.
CyberWorld Version 1.0 is launched with bugs fixed.
 CyberWorld Genesis NFTs were minted and released along with the launch. A powerful token distribution software was developed to automatically send any crypto tokens to massive number of addresses.  CyberWorld Version 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CyberMilesNFT Newsletter - Under the Boom of Digital Collectibles, What the Challenges NFT Faces?</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20210806-nft-news7-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Aug 2021 10:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20210806-nft-news7-en/</guid>
      <description>Last week, CyberMiles shared an article about the pros and cons of OpeaSea and CyberWorld (Click here for more details). Today, we&#39;ll talk about some issues of the NFT market.
As mentioned in the previous CyberMiles articles, NFT speared ahead in the arts, sports, games, music, fashion, and other industries. NFT is continues expanding its presence. Digital art is moving from the niche to the masses. There is no doubt that NFT has led to the emergence of new forms of digital work transactions and marketplaces, providing high-profile and underground artists with a new way of income.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CyberMilesNFT Newsletter — What Are the Advantages of CyberWorld comparing with OpenSea?</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20210802-nft-new6-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Aug 2021 10:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20210802-nft-new6-en/</guid>
      <description>With the rise of the NFT market, led by some notable projects like NBA Topshop, CyrproPunks, the NFT market has seen a wave of digital collectibles and NFT exchange platforms. Devin Finzer launched an NFT exchange platform in 2017 called &amp;lsquo;OpenSea&amp;rsquo;, attracting a lot of attention as an early NFT project platform. As a result, the total market sales grew from $8 million in January to $150 million in March 2021.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CyberMilesNFT Newsletter- The NFT Boom: Luxury Brands Lead the Digital Fashion Trend?</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20210720-nft-new5-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jul 2021 10:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20210720-nft-new5-en/</guid>
      <description>The age of digital consumption seems to be changing the marketing model of every industry. Fashion brands seem to transfer to digital networks and technology as a way out of their transformation and upgrading. The luxury group LVMH formed a partnership with Google in June that will use AI to provide personalized services and content in order to enhance user experience. LVMH, Cartier’s parent company Richemont and Prada jointly announced that the three parties plan to create a solution powered by &amp;lsquo;Aura Blockchain&amp;rsquo;, a global luxury blockchain open to all luxury brands.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CyberMilesNFT Newsletter- World Wide Web Source Code Made NFT Auctioned for Millions. What does this mean for Programmers?</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20210715-nft-news4-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2021 10:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20210715-nft-news4-en/</guid>
      <description>A big NFT news in June: Tim Berners-Lee, Father of the Internet, minted ‘World Wide Web’ source code to NFT on 15th June and sold at Sotheby’s on 30th June. Bidding started from $1000 and lasted for a week. The final price was over $5.4 million.
Named “ This Changes Everything”, the NFT consists of four parts. Work includes 1. The original archive of dated and time-stamped files containing the source code.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CyberMilesNFT Newsletter - Simple Steps: Connect MetaMask to CyberMiles Public Blockchain</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20210709-tutorial-metamask-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jul 2021 10:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20210709-tutorial-metamask-en/</guid>
      <description>Hi, CyberMiles fans!🍓
Great update! CyberMiles engineers have upgraded the RPC node! Now you can use MetaMask to connect to CyberMiles public blockchain! You can transfer CMT, deploy smart contract on MetaMask, and other features are compatible!
To guide you on how to connect MetaMask to the CyberMiles public blockchain. Here is a detailed tutorial for you.
 Log in your MetaMask account first.  Click the &amp;ldquo;Networks&amp;rdquo; option.  Click&amp;rsquo; Custom RPC&amp;rsquo; to enter the node setting interface.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CyberMilesNFT Newsletter - Instagram and Twitter Dab Hand with NFT  </title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20210708-cybermiles-news3-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jul 2021 10:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20210708-cybermiles-news3-en/</guid>
      <description>Compared to $13.7 million in the first half of 2020, the NFT market surges to $2.5 billion by now this year. Several days before, Tim Berners-Lee, &amp;ldquo;Father of the World Wide Web&amp;rdquo;, sold the original web source code as an NFT for $5.4 million. The popularity of NFT as a medium for selling digital collectibles has been growing. The boom in the NFT market attracted a wave of social media platforms to jump on the bandwagon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CyberMiles NFT Newsletter - CyberWorld NFT Platform Upgrade</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20210702-cybermiles-news-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2021 10:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20210702-cybermiles-news-en/</guid>
      <description>As CyberMilers must have noticed, there have been warm-up and publicity on social media for CyberWorld updates and upgrades over the next few months, which began last week.
The engineers and marketing operators of CyberMiles have been delivering the CyberWorld NFT platform with tremendous efficiency and did a successful spread in the last few months. To improve the users’ experience, CyberMiles is currently upgrading the platform in terms of technology and content, bringing a new CyberWorld to everyone who always supported CyberMiles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CyberMilesNFT Newsletter - NFT&#39;s &#39;Blue Ocean&#39;, the Global Market Capitalization of NFT is Near $18 Billion</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20210701-nft-news-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 10:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20210701-nft-news-en/</guid>
      <description>CyberMilesNFT Newsletter - NFT&#39;s &amp;lsquo;Blue Ocean&amp;rsquo;, the Global Market Capitalization of NFT is Near $18 Billion According to the report by CionGecko, the global market capitalization of NFT is near $18 billion, trades $1.2 billion a single day. The number of transactions is over 710,000 pieces. The number of users and trades is also rising.
Nikhil Sethi, vice predict of a blockchain startup said,&amp;rdquo; The global NFT market has exploded in 2021, with over $700 million entering the space.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CybermilesNFT Newsletter — From arts to sports, NFT crosses boundaries constantly</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20210630-nft-news1-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 10:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20210630-nft-news1-en/</guid>
      <description>Sales of digital collectibles have fallen in recent weeks, NFT sales is a slowdown Ryan Browne is a technology reporter for CNBC in London published an article about NFT sales. He said sales of digital collectibles known as non-fungible tokens have fallen dramatically in recent weeks (Browne, 2021).
Earlier this year, NFT has swept the art world. The graphic designer Beeple sold an NFT for a record $69 million at a Christie’s auction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CyberWorld V1.0 Airdrop Campaign Came to A Successful Conclusion</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20210629-nft-01-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 10:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20210629-nft-01-en/</guid>
      <description>Hello CyberWorld Fans！
 CyberMilesNews: CyberWorld.finance V1.0 airdrop campaign came to a successful conclusion! We have completed the distribution of CyberWorld Genesis Series NFTs and CMT. Thanks to every CyberWorld community participant for your support!**
 As the number of winner addresses was over 100,000, so our engineer specifically developed a new tokens distribution tool to transfer the tokens. The new airdrop tool distributed a total of 114300 CMT successfully. The winners can track CMTs received here at CMTTracking.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Digital Image Sold for 69.35 Million Dollars at Christies&#39; Auction</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20210324-nft-01-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 10:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20210324-nft-01-en/</guid>
      <description>We can categorize the NFTs into Art NFT, FI NFT, IP NFT and Game NFT.
According to the research team at CyberMiles, many problems are identified with the current NFT market. All of them are to some extent preventing NFT from being enjoyed by more users, and may cause losses and risks to users who join the craze blindly. The following is derived from CyberMile&amp;rsquo; research.
 ART NFT has not yet developed a stable market preference and is highly susceptible to manipulation by pumping sharks; and the individual token prices are often overvalued and not for ordinary users to participate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sino-Global Joins CyberMiles in Launching a Highly-Secure NFT Exchange</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20210318-nft-exchange-sino-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2021 10:00:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20210318-nft-exchange-sino-en/</guid>
      <description>March 18, 2021 – Sino-Global Shipping America, Ltd. (NASDAQ: SINO) collaborates with the public blockchain CyberMiles to launch a new exchange for NFTs (non-fungible tokens). The new NFT exchange will serve as a highly-secure, robust platform for collectors, artists, musicians and investors to create, sell and buy one of a kind, digital content represented as NFTs. The companies expect to officially launch their new NFT platform in July 2021, providing a critical link between the virtual blockchain world and the physical world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sino Global Shipping Partners up with CyberMiles Blockchain to Go Full Power into the Skyrocketing NFT Business</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20210223-nft-sino-global-shipping-partner-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2021 10:00:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20210223-nft-sino-global-shipping-partner-en/</guid>
      <description>Sino Global Shipping America, a Nasdaq traded company, will work with CyberMiles, an e-commerce public blockchain, to jointly launch a blockchain non-fungible token (NFT) CRC-721 protocol and trading platform, which will allow enterprises, institutions, and individuals to conveniently issue NFTs on the CyberMiles public blockchain and also trade NFTs easily.
[A non-fungible token (NFT)] (https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Non-fungible_token) is a special type of [cryptographic token] (https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cryptocurrency) issued on blockchain which represents something unique and one of a kind; Non-fungible tokens are not mutually interchangeable, thus has the perfect use cases for art pieces and anything that are collectibles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tutorial: How to record your graduate certificate on CyberMiles public blockchain</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/tutorial-tianjin-student-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Sep 2020 15:00:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/tutorial-tianjin-student-en/</guid>
      <description>The graduation certificate of Tianjin University will be permanently recorded on the CyberMiles blockchain, which can be stored permanently and cannot be tampered with! How is this achieved?
The entire Dapp design is divided into two parts: * The smart contract records key information to ensure that the information cannot be corrected. This part is equivalent to the replacement of traditional applications; * The front-end display page is implemented using HTML, JavaScript, and CSS, 100% copying the real world certificate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>All Possiblities at the Age of ETH 2.0</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20200618-eth-2-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 15:00:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20200618-eth-2-en/</guid>
      <description>On 18th June, CyberMiles chief scientist was invited to attend the Show hosted by Jinse Media and participated in the discussion on &amp;ldquo;All possibilities in the age of Ethereum 2.0&amp;rdquo;, together with the following 3 guests.
 SECBIT Laboratory, Guo Yu PlatOn， Dr. Xia Loopring Protocol, Wang Dong  Hello, I&#39;m Michael Yuan. I&#39;m the CEO of Second State and one of the co-founder of the public blockchain CyberMiles. Our team is the developers for Ethereum&#39;s next-generation virtual machine, Ewasm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CMT 2020 Second Quarter Release Announcement</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20200529-cmt-release-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2020 15:00:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20200529-cmt-release-en/</guid>
      <description>Dear CMT holders!
According to the CyberMiles Whitepaper, the CyberMiles Foundation address 0x1a14Ec3003C943a0624C7c513D502559c8b1b041 holds 200 million CMTs, to be released 10% every quarter, as planned to the CyberMiles team and partners, like 5miles.
The 20 million CMTs in the second quarter of 2020 is expected to be released on June 17th. This release is as scheduled and is completely in accordance with the CyberMiles white paper&#39;s plan. You are welcome to supervise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OKEx Pool as CyberMiles&#39; Validator: Stake and win a Cube</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/2020-05-28-okex-pool-staking-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 May 2020 15:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/2020-05-28-okex-pool-staking-en/</guid>
      <description>OKEx Pool became one of CyberMiles’ validator and is currently ranking the third with 27238182 voting powers and declared a compensation rate of 30 percent.
OKEx Pool is a world’s leading comprehensive mining pool built upon the world’s leading cryptocurrency exchange OKEx, offering a one-stop mining and trading experience for users, supporting the mining of PoW, PoS, and PoS-variant cryptocurrencies. It has become supernodes of multiple cryptocurrencies, including EOS and COSMOS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Issue your own CRC20 token on CyberMiles</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190521-issue-token-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 May 2020 10:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190521-issue-token-en/</guid>
      <description>Last week, we introduced an artist who issued his own CRC20 tokens LCT to motivate his community. When the members published their own painting, then the member will receive the LCT token as a reward. The LCT token could be used to exchange the artist’s painting.
You can easily issue your CRC20 token with CyberMiles App, if you have at least 1,000 CMT in your CMT address.
But if you want to write some code and start from scratch, you can also use BUIDL for CMT to issue your own tokens.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release of EWASM test net based on CyberMiles public blockchain</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20200423-ewasm-testnet-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Apr 2020 10:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20200423-ewasm-testnet-en/</guid>
      <description>A NEW public EWASM test net based on Second State&#39;s virtual machine technology and CyberMiles public blockchain software just launched. CYBERMILES becomes one of the world&#39;s first public blockchains to support Ethereum&#39;s next-generation virtual machine. Developers can deploy the new Ewasm smart contract by running the Ethereum&#39;s next-generation virtual machine on the new Ewasm test net of CyberMiles.
WebAssembly allows near-native code performance without compromising security. In addition, the WebAssembly community is much more vibrant and larger.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>