<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>NFT on CyberMiles News and Articles</title>
    <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/tags/nft/</link>
    <description>Recent content in NFT on CyberMiles News and Articles</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Oct 2021 10:01:23 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://blog.cybermiles.io/tags/nft/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>CyberWorld Tutorial Content</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20211015-tutorial-content-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Oct 2021 10:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20211015-tutorial-content-en/</guid>
      <description>In order to improve the user experience and use CyberWorld NFT marketplace with ease. We have compiled the following series of CyberWorld tutorials. Hope these step-by-step guides give you the key to the NFT world.
Web-user 1：CyberMilesNFT Newsletter - Simple Steps: Connect MetaMask to CyberMiles Public Blockchain
https://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20210709-tutorial-metamask-en/
2：CybeWorld on the Web - User Guide
https://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20211013-tutorial-v2.0-04-en/
Mobile-user 1：CyberMiles App User Guide
https://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20211013-tutorial-v2.0-01-en/
2：CyberWorld on the Mobile-User Guide
https://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20211013-tutorial-v2.0-02-en/
3：CyberPay Payment User Guide</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CyberWorld 使用教程</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20211015-tutorial-content-zh/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Oct 2021 10:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20211015-tutorial-content-zh/</guid>
      <description>为了提升用户体验，让大家更加方便的使用 CyberWorld，我们将 CyberWorld 相关的一系列使用教程作了以下汇总，相信从这篇文档中您能收获您需要的任何内</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CyberMiles 钱包 App 使用教程（建议收藏）</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20211014-tutorial-v2.0-01-zh/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2021 10:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20211014-tutorial-v2.0-01-zh/</guid>
      <description>大多数情况下，我们的数字货币是存放在交易所平台上的，如果出现平台被黑客攻击货币被盗的情况（交易平台聚集了大量的数字资产，对黑客来说是非常诱人</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CyberPay 兑换操作使用说明</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20211014-tutorial-v2.0-03-zh/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2021 10:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20211014-tutorial-v2.0-03-zh/</guid>
      <description>CyberPay是由CyberWorld开发的平台，支持USDT兑换Diamond、Diamond兑换USDT，即将支持美元兑换Diamon</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PC 版本 CyberWorld 使用说明</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20211014-tutorial-v2.0-04-zh/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2021 10:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20211014-tutorial-v2.0-04-zh/</guid>
      <description>CyberWorld 是由 CyberMiles构建和运营的区块链 NFT 平台。用于收藏和交易真正稀缺的数字艺术品。每件艺术品都由艺术家真实创建，并通过区块链技术通证化</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>手机版本CyberWorld使用说明</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20211014-tutorial-v2.0-02-zh/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2021 10:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20211014-tutorial-v2.0-02-zh/</guid>
      <description>CyberWorld 是由 CyberMiles构建和运营的区块链 NFT 平台。用于收藏和交易真正稀缺的数字艺术品。每件艺术品都由艺术家真实创建，并通过区块链技术通证化</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CyberMiles App User Guide</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20211013-tutorial-v2.0-01-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 10:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20211013-tutorial-v2.0-01-en/</guid>
      <description>CyberMiles Foundation recommends that users withdraw their tokens from the exchanges to their own decentralized cryptocurrency wallets, and keep them safe.
Cryptocurrency asset is stored with a public address coupled with a private key. Whoever gets the private key will be the owner. If users keep the private key themselves, there might be the risk of forgetting or losing the private key. With CyberMiles app you can store your CMT securely and only need to remember a password you set.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CyberPay Payment User Guide</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20211013-tutorial-v2.0-03-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 10:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20211013-tutorial-v2.0-03-en/</guid>
      <description>CyberPay is the payment service of CyberWorld NFT marketplace. USDT can be exchanged 1:1 with Diamond and exchanged back. We will allow the purchase of Diamond with a credit card (USD) soon.
Note: Diamond (shortened as DO) is a stable cryptocurrency issued by CyberWorld and pegged to USD to allow users to trade NFT on CyberWorld. 1 Diamond = 1 USD = 1 USDT. This guide will talk about 1：How to use USDT to exchange for Diamond 2: How to use Diamond to exchange for USDT</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CyberWorld on the Mobile-User Guide</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20211013-tutorial-v2.0-02-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 10:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20211013-tutorial-v2.0-02-en/</guid>
      <description>CyberWorld is an NFT marketplace built and operated by CyberMiles together with Sino-global. It can be used to collect and trade truly rare digital art. Each art piece is created by an artist and NFTized with blockchain technology. It will be a crypto digital platform that serves the content creators and their supporters the best.
CyberWorld has Web and mobile versions. This is the user guide for the Mobile version. The guide will explain: 1: How to create an NFT collection 2：How to min an NFT 3：How to transfer my NFT 4：How to sell my NFT 5：How to buy a fixed priced NFT 6：How to offer to buy NFT at a certain price.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CybeWorld on the Web - User Guide</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20211013-tutorial-v2.0-04-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 10:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20211013-tutorial-v2.0-04-en/</guid>
      <description>CyberWorld is an NFT marketplace built and operated by CyberMiles together with Sino-global. It can be used to collect and trade truly rare digital artworks. Each art piece is created by an artist and NFTized with blockchain technology. It will be an NFT platform that serves the content creators and their supporters the best.
CyberWorld has Web and mobile versions. This is the user guide for the Web version. The guide will explain:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CyberMilesNFT Newsletter - CyberWorld NFT Marketplace V2.0 to be Launched</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20210927-nft-news13-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 10:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20210927-nft-news13-en/</guid>
      <description>Finally! CyberWorld V2.0 will be launched in a few days. The CyberWorld engineering and product team has updated the operation staff on this great news, so we are here to announce it to CyberWorld supporters with all the excitement.
First of all, we’d like to thank all supporters for your patience waiting for such a long time after the launch of V1.0 several months ago. CyberWorld NFT marketplace will be worth the wait.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CyberMilesNFT Newsletter- How CyberWorld Empowers Content Creators on Patreon and more? </title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20210916-nft-news12-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2021 10:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20210916-nft-news12-en/</guid>
      <description>Patreon is more than a crowdfunding platform Patreon was founded by Jack Conte and Sam Yam in 2013. Creators can sell their content or works directly to their fans on Patreon. In addition, subscribers can donate a certain amount of money to the creators and artists they support to help them grow.
Patreon is a membership-based platform that allows creators to monetize on their creations. The starting point is to provide ongoing funding for creators and artists: they can &amp;ldquo;ask&amp;rdquo; fans for money if their works are uploaded.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CyberMilesNFT 简讯－CyberWorld 如何赋能 Patreon 和其它平台的内容创作者？</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20210916-nft-news12-zh/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2021 10:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20210916-nft-news12-zh/</guid>
      <description>Patreon 不止是一个众筹平台 Patreon 艺术家平台是由 Jack Conte 和 Sam Yam 于2013年创立的。不同的内容创作者，如画家、音乐创作者、文章作者，甚至程序员，可以在 Patreon 上向粉</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CyberMilesNFT Newsletter - Calling for Creators to Make NFTs on CyberWorld </title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20210903-nft-news11-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 10:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20210903-nft-news11-en/</guid>
      <description>CyberWorld NFT Marketplace will allow credit card payment in November. In addition, CyberWorld will provide the NFT airdrop distribution tool, which helps artists and content creators to produce many NFTs at one time and airdrop them to their followers and fans. Wanna have a try and mint an NFT and transfer it to your fans, family, and friends? Join CyberWorld now to enjoy creator perks!
Background About CyberWorld and the Team: CyberWorld is a blockchain NFT marketplace jointly built by CyberMiles and Sino-Global Shipping America, Ltd.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CyberMilesNFT 简讯- CyberWorld 招募内容创作者入驻，生成 NFT</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20210903-nft-new11-zh/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 10:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20210903-nft-new11-zh/</guid>
      <description>CyberWorld NFT 交易平台将在十月前上线法币兑换功能，消费者可以使用信用卡购买 NFT； 对于艺术家或各种形式的内容创作者来说，CyberWorld 将提供服务</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Market Research (Reference: TokenInsight)</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20210823-nft-news10-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2021 10:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20210823-nft-news10-en/</guid>
      <description>Background： Thanks to TokenInsight for its detailed report on the NFT market in Q2 and July. According to TokenInsight 2021 Q2 &amp;amp; July NFT Industry Report, we make a conclusion with the report about the hottest projects, developments, and latest data on the NFT market. TokenInsight is a great partner of CyberMiles and a supportive validator on the CM public blockchain. Welcome to stake with them. Here is the tutorial: How to stake with CyberMiles App to get Block Award.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>市场调研（数据来源：TokenInsight）</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20210823-nft-new10-zh/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2021 10:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20210823-nft-new10-zh/</guid>
      <description>背景： 首先感谢 TokenInsight 对 NFT 市场第二季度以及7月的动态做了详细的行业报告，这份调研主要根据 TokenInsight 的行业报告进行分析和总结。TokenInsight 是 CyberMiles 的</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CyberMilesNFT Newsletter - CyberWorld Supports BOA in Building Their NFT Marketplace</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20210818-nft-news9-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 10:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20210818-nft-news9-en/</guid>
      <description>With the heat of NFT continues to rise, all industries are jumping on the NFT bandwagon. CyberWorld partnered with the Bank of Asia (BOA) in building their BOA’s NFT marketplace, BOAX, in July 2021. With the grand opening of the 2021 Olympic Games, BOA Financial Group officially launched the new premium NFT marketplace BOAX, which allows users to trade digital assets online. The first NFT artwork, “Olympic Happiness,” exclusive was released on the BOAX NFT Marketplace on 23 July 2021, which was created by Dr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CyberMilesNFT 简讯－CyberWorld 支持合作伙伴 BOA 建立其首个 NFT 交易平台</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20210818-nft-news9-zh/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 10:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20210818-nft-news9-zh/</guid>
      <description>随着 NFT 的热度持续攀升，各行各业争先恐后的加入了 NFT 的热潮。今年七月，CyberWorld 与亚洲银行（BOA）建立合作伙伴关系，全力支持 BOA 建立其</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CyberMilesNFT Newsletter - NFT Market’s Regulatory Challenges</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20210813-nft-news8-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Aug 2021 10:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20210813-nft-news8-en/</guid>
      <description>In the previous CyberMiles Newsletter series article analyzing the challenges of hype, money laundering, illegal financing, infringement, and fraud that the NFT market faces in detail, we pre-announced discussion on the regulation of the NFT market. NFT market has to be regulated to protect all parties involved, not only those who simply want to buy the NFTs for collections but also the owners of artworks and artists who want to release NFTs.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>