<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Developer on CyberMiles News and Articles</title>
    <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/tags/developer/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Developer on CyberMiles News and Articles</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Sep 2020 15:00:23 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://blog.cybermiles.io/tags/developer/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Tutorial: How to record your graduate certificate on CyberMiles public blockchain</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/tutorial-tianjin-student-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Sep 2020 15:00:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/tutorial-tianjin-student-en/</guid>
      <description>The graduation certificate of Tianjin University will be permanently recorded on the CyberMiles blockchain, which can be stored permanently and cannot be tampered with! How is this achieved?
The entire Dapp design is divided into two parts: * The smart contract records key information to ensure that the information cannot be corrected. This part is equivalent to the replacement of traditional applications; * The front-end display page is implemented using HTML, JavaScript, and CSS, 100% copying the real world certificate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>教程：如何将毕业证书存入 CyberMiles 公链</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/tutorial-tianjin-student-zh/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2020 15:00:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/tutorial-tianjin-student-zh/</guid>
      <description>天津大学的毕业证书将永久记录到 CyberMiles 区块链，实现了永久可保存、不可篡改！这是如何实现的呢？ 整个Dapp 设计分为两部分： * 智能合约记录关键信息，确</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Writing a Hello World Smart Contract for CyberMiles</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190215-helloworld-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2019 15:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190215-helloworld-en/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Hello World&amp;rdquo; is often the first program those learning to code write. It&amp;rsquo;s no exception for building your first blockchain smart contract. This is a step-by-step guide of how to develop a &amp;ldquo;Hello World&amp;rdquo; smart contract with Lity.
Prerequisites Before you start, prepare the following tools to develop on the CyberMiles blockchain.
Install Chrome browser The CyberMiles visual developer tools work on the Chrome browser platform. Download and install Chrome browser.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>