<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>artists on CyberMiles News and Articles</title>
    <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/tags/artists/</link>
    <description>Recent content in artists on CyberMiles News and Articles</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 10:01:23 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://blog.cybermiles.io/tags/artists/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>CyberMilesNFT Newsletter - Calling for Creators to Make NFTs on CyberWorld </title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20210903-nft-news11-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 10:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20210903-nft-news11-en/</guid>
      <description>Background About CyberWorld and the Team: CyberWorld is a blockchain NFT marketplace jointly built by CyberMiles and Sino-Global Shipping America, Ltd.(NASDAQ: SINO). It is is developed and maintained by a decentralized team of open-source software developers with the CyberMiles Foundation.
CyberMiles is pivoting to NFT as its core ecosystem development focus and forging ahead, aiming to bridge the blockchain and real world. After several years in stealth mode, CyberMiles’ leading NFT marketplace and products to solve the current pain points in the NFT field based on a strong high-performance public blockchain and collaborative engineering team will become a self-driven growth protocol that is constantly optimized and iterated to pioneer the development of NFT and blockchain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CyberMilesNFT Newsletter — What Are the Advantages of CyberWorld comparing with OpenSea?</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20210802-nft-new6-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Aug 2021 10:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20210802-nft-new6-en/</guid>
      <description>With the rise of the NFT market, led by some notable projects like NBA Topshop, CyrproPunks, the NFT market has seen a wave of digital collectibles and NFT exchange platforms. Devin Finzer launched an NFT exchange platform in 2017 called &amp;lsquo;OpenSea&amp;rsquo;, attracting a lot of attention as an early NFT project platform. As a result, the total market sales grew from $8 million in January to $150 million in March 2021.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>