<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>E Commerce on CyberMiles News and Articles</title>
    <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/tags/e-commerce/</link>
    <description>Recent content in E Commerce on CyberMiles News and Articles</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2019 15:30:23 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://blog.cybermiles.io/tags/e-commerce/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>FairPlay：一种新型DApp</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190621-fairplay-dapp-zh/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2019 15:30:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190621-fairplay-dapp-zh/</guid>
      <description>什么是FairPlay FairPlay 使用智能合约进行公平透明的自动抽奖。 它允许任何人创建并参与抽奖等电商营销活动。 根据Google Analystics，</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FairPlay: a new type of DApp</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190620-fairplay-dapp-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2019 15:30:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190620-fairplay-dapp-en/</guid>
      <description>Credits: FairPlay is developed by Second State, an open source enterprise smart contract platform, and deployed on the CyberMiles public blockchain.
What is FairPlay FairPlay uses smart contracts to conduct automated prize draws that are fair and transparent. It allows anyone to create and participate in product giveaways and e-commerce marketing campaigns. Since its launch, FairPlay has routinely reached a DAU (Daily Active Users) of 1000 (according to Google Analytics), with each giveaway receiving hundreds of on-chain transactions, making it one of the most popular DApps of all public blockchains.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CyberMiles 公链新上线超级节点SNZ Holding</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190618-cmts-staking-zh/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2019 15:30:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190618-cmts-staking-zh/</guid>
      <description>CyberMiles 公链新上线了超级节点SNZ Holding。SNZ Holding 将自我权益投票300万CMT，报酬比率为25%。 SNZ Holding致力于提供专业的POS矿</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Today CyberMiles Blockchain Welcomes Another Validator, SNZ Holding</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190618-cmts-staking-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2019 15:30:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190618-cmts-staking-en/</guid>
      <description>CyberMiles community embraces a newcomer Validator today! SNZ Holding, CyberMiles&amp;rsquo; newest Validator, is up and running, joining in the maintainance of the network security of CyberMiles blockchain.
To be a Validator, SNZ Holding has self-staked 3 million CMTs as a commitment to CMT Community. It claims a compensation rate of 25% for all its delegators.
SNZ Holding is an institution dedicated to providing high-standard and professional POS validation services. SNZ has been engaged in investment, consultancy, community building and other business related to blockchain since 2016 and is an early investor in Ethereum, Dfinity, Cosmos, Polkadot and other renowned projects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Win a shiny lipstick from HashQuark ($37 USD value)</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190617-giveaway10-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2019 15:30:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190617-giveaway10-en/</guid>
      <description>Ready for the last prize with @FairPlayDapp launch campaign?
FairPlay Dapp is the world’s most transparent lucky draw tool for you to draw a prize! Fair, automated, and decentralized prize drawings. Powered by and guaranteed by blockchain smart contracts! No shenanigans. Try your luck today. The winners are chosen by smart contracts with its embedded random number generator. See how it works.
Today’s the very last and special prize is from HashQuark!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Win a Limited Edition Metal Art from AnChain.ai ($499 USD value)</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190614-fairplay9-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2019 15:30:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190614-fairplay9-en/</guid>
      <description>Smart contract safety is extremely important for DApps. The winner drawing of the FairPlay smart contract is based on a safe random number generated by CyberMiles Validators. The secure random number generator for smart contracts is a key innovation of CyberMiles.
CyberMiles has a strong technology partnership with AnChain.ai, an AI-powered blockchain security firm. In 2018, AnChain.ai detected the first Blockchain APT (BAPT) hack in history: BAPT-FOMO3D that stole $4 millions worth of ETHs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Win a Philips Electric Shaver for Father&#39;s Day gift, sponsored by Lvl.99</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190613-giveaway8-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2019 15:30:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190613-giveaway8-en/</guid>
      <description>Father’s Day is just around the corner! Do you have a gift in mind for Dad? The man who has been the most caring guardian for you deserves something nice! No idea yet? This is where CyberMiles comes to rescue! Enter to win a Philips Electric Shaver ($50).
This prize is sponsored by lvl.99, a CyberMiles genesis Validator. Lvl 99 is based in Jakarta, Indonesia. It represents a group of Indonesia investors who had supported CyberMiles since day one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Win 666 IRIS tokens x 3, sponsored by IRIS Network</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190612-giveaway7-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2019 15:30:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190612-giveaway7-en/</guid>
      <description>The FairPlay Smart Contracts and search engine are key technology milestones to CyberMiles&amp;rsquo; decentralized e-commerce marketplace.
 The FairPlay DApp, launched on 4th of June, empowers anyone to create and take part in product promotions and giveaways. With over a thousand Daily Active Users (DAUs) according to Google Analytics, the FairPlay DApp is already one of the most popular DApps in all of blockchains.
The FairPlay Smart Contracts and search engine are key technology milestones to CyberMiles&amp;rsquo; decentralized e-commerce marketplace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Win 600 LiMaGo tokens for traveling guide service, sponsored by LiMaGo</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190611-giveaway6-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2019 15:30:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190611-giveaway6-en/</guid>
      <description>CyberMiles, a public blockchain for ecommerce, is doing a 2-week giveaway campaign to celebrate the grand launch of the new DApp, FairPlay.
The FairPlay Dapp, ran on CyberMiles, empowers everyone to create and take part in online raffles. You can use it to do givaways for product promotions, game among friends or anything you can think of. With inbeded search engine and ecommerce products smart contract creation function, FairPlayDapp is a key technology milestone to CyberMiles&amp;rsquo; decentralized e-commerce marketplace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Win a CMT Cube, sponsored by SSSnodes</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190610-giveaway5-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2019 15:30:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190610-giveaway5-en/</guid>
      <description>The FairPlay Dapp, launched on 4th of June, empowers anyone to create and take part in online raffles, giveaways for product promotions etc. With over a thousand Daily Active Users (DAUs) according to Google Analytics, the FairPlay DApp is already amoung the most popular DApps in all of blockchains.
The FairPlay Smart Contracts and search engine are key technology milestones to CyberMiles&amp;rsquo; decentralized e-commerce marketplace. Read more about it here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Win a pass to DeveloperWeek New York each</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190607-giveaway4-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2019 15:30:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190607-giveaway4-en/</guid>
      <description>The FairPlay Dapp, launched on 4th of June, empowers anyone to create and take part in online raffles, giveaways for product promotions etc. With over a thousand Daily Active Users (DAUs) according to Google Analytics, the FairPlay DApp is already amoung the most popular DApps in all of blockchains.
The FairPlay Smart Contracts and search engine are key technology milestones to CyberMiles&amp;rsquo; decentralized e-commerce marketplace. Read more about it here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Win two 2,888 HPTs Prizes, sponsored by Huobi Pool</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190606-giveaway3-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2019 15:30:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190606-giveaway3-en/</guid>
      <description>The FairPlay Dapp, launched on 4th of June, empowers anyone to create and take part in product promotions and giveaways. With over a thousand Daily Active Users (DAUs) according to Google Analytics, the FairPlay DApp is already one of the most popular DApps in all of blockchains.
The FairPlay Smart Contracts and search engine are key technology milestones to CyberMiles&amp;rsquo; decentralized e-commerce marketplace. You can read more about it here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Win a  unique Tiffany Corkscrew, sponsored by 5miles</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190605-giveaway2-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2019 15:30:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190605-giveaway2-en/</guid>
      <description>CyberMiles proudly launched FairPlay Dapp on 4th of June, for every one to create and take part in lucky draws with a few clicks. This lucky draw Dapp is a key milesstone to CyberMiles&amp;rsquo; decentralized marketplace.
Meanwhile, a grandiose 10-days campaign ran on @FairPlayDap empowered with CyberMiles public blockchain was kicked off. A new lucky draw is to be announced everyday for 10 days to draw lucky winners with FairPlayDapp!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create a new FairPlay drawing</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190604-fairplay-creator-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2019 15:30:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190604-fairplay-creator-en/</guid>
      <description>The FairPlay smart contract enables anyone to create a prize drawing of anything – digital products, physical merchandise, anything that can be sold via e-commerce.The FairPlay games are about fairness, automation, transparency, and decentralization in e-commerce.
  This article is a guide on how to create a new giveaway.
When you enter the FairPlay DApp, you see a &amp;ldquo;Create a new giveaway&amp;rdquo; button above the search box. You can also find creatng a new giveaway on the top left of the DApp page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FairPlay: decentralized prize drawing for e-commerce</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190604-fairplay-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2019 15:30:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190604-fairplay-en/</guid>
      <description>The FairPlay smart contract enables anyone to create a prize drawing of anything &amp;ndash; digital products, physical merchandise, anything that can be sold via e-commerce.
Of course, you can also browse or search for FairPlay drawings by keywords or CMT address directly in the FairPlay DApp. This is a key milestone to CyberMiles&amp;rsquo; decentralized e-commerce marketplace.
FairPlay prize drawing is fair, fully automated, transparent, and decentralized. All you need is the CMT Wallet mobile application.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FairPlayDApp-最公平的抽奖工具</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190604-fairplay-zh/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2019 15:30:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190604-fairplay-zh/</guid>
      <description>通过FairPlay智能合约，任何人都可以创建发起任何通过电商销售的商品抽奖，可以是数字产品，实体商品。 FairPlay DApp内置智能合约搜索引擎。通过</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Play to win prizes by scanning QR codes</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190604-fairplay1-player-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2019 15:30:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190604-fairplay1-player-en/</guid>
      <description>The FairPlay games are about fairness, automation, transparency, and decentralization in e-commerce.
You can access the FairPlay DApp directly from your CMT Wallet. Find FairPlay lucky draws to participate in:
 By scanning QR codes shared by people(this article will introduce this method) By browsing active drawings from your CMT Wallet  By searching for drawings from your CMT Wallet  Scan the above QR code with your CMT Wallet to see a completed FairPlay lucky draw.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Play to win prizes via the search engine</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190604-fairplay2-player-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2019 15:30:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190604-fairplay2-player-en/</guid>
      <description>The FairPlay games are about fairness, automation, transparency, and decentralization in e-commerce.
You can access the FairPlay DApp directly from your CMT Wallet. Find FairPlay drawings to participate in:
 By browsing active drawings from your CMT Wallet By searching for drawings from your CMT Wallet By scanning QR codes shared by people    Search for giveaways from your CMT Wallet When you enter the FairPlay DApp, you see a search box.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>