<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>giveaway on CyberMiles News and Articles</title>
    <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/tags/giveaway/</link>
    <description>Recent content in giveaway on CyberMiles News and Articles</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2019 15:00:23 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://blog.cybermiles.io/tags/giveaway/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>More giveaways with FairPlay DApp are coming</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190703-faiplay-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2019 15:00:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190703-faiplay-en/</guid>
      <description>Thanks for all players who has participated the two-week giveaway and our lovely sponsors. We have 1900+ players in the last campaign in June.
This campaign has ended with great popularity. For those who missed the chance to enter, no need to be regretful, because the giveaways are gonna keep coming! Yay!
Have you entered the ongoing giveaway of ByteTrade yet? You can get one of the 20 cool T-shirts! Everyone has a high chance to win!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FairPlay: Win a pizza on the Bitcoin Pizza Day</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190521-pizza-giveaway-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2019 10:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190521-pizza-giveaway-en/</guid>
      <description>FairPlay will choose 4 lucky winners, and give away Domino&#39;s pizza gift cards ($15 each) on May 22nd!
May 22nd is known as the Bitcoin Pizza Day. On that day, we celebrate the most “expensive” pizza bought in human history!
On May 22nd 2010, Laszlo Hanyecz, a computer programmer in Florida, paid a Bitcoin Talk forum user 10,000 BTC to get two pizzas. In today&#39;s Bitcoin value, he paid more than $400 million US Dollars for each pizza.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FairPlay: Win movie tickets for two on Mother’s Day!</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190510-fairplay-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2019 08:01:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190510-fairplay-en/</guid>
      <description>Mother’s Day is right around the corner. Are you ready for the celebration? Win movie tickets for 2, and take your mom to a movie!
Each winner will get a $25 AMC or Cinemark gift card — enough for two movie tickets. Please note that this offer is only available in the USA. Good luck!
How does it work? You can participate the drawing for free by downloading the CMT Wallet mobile app, and entering your contact info.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>