<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>peer-to-peer marketplace on CyberMiles News and Articles</title>
    <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/tags/peer-to-peer-marketplace/</link>
    <description>Recent content in peer-to-peer marketplace on CyberMiles News and Articles</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 May 2019 17:07:23 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://blog.cybermiles.io/tags/peer-to-peer-marketplace/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Ask CyberMiles Question 8: What are the next steps for CyberMiles to reach new markets?</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190510-amaq8-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2019 17:07:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190510-amaq8-en/</guid>
      <description>Q: What are the next steps for Cybermiles to reach new markets?
A: There are a couple of things. First, we want to reach the international market, outside of east Asia. China and Vietnam are the largest group of CMTs holders so far, and we have benefited tremendously from them. Our ecommerce platform is mostly in the United States.
So to open up CMT staking from the wallet is one of the most important steps and also enabling supernodes from various areas and community participation to reach out CMT.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ask CyberMiles Question 9:  Does the advantage of CyberMiles beat the inherent advantages of traditional players like eBay or Amazon?</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190514-amaq9-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2019 17:07:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190514-amaq9-en/</guid>
      <description>Q: Does the advantage of CyberMiles beat the inherent advantages of traditional players like eBay or Amazon?
A: Cheaper prices for buyers and more profit for sellers. Amazon has monopoly position on the market, therefore it has too strong a bargaining power rendering sellers and buyers vulnerable. In addition, the centralized Amazon make 40% of its profit out of the vast amount of data the data it gathered from the users, which should belong to the users.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ask CyberMiles Question 6: What are the next targets of CyberMiles regarding adoption??</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190509-amaq6-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2019 17:06:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190509-amaq6-en/</guid>
      <description>Q: What are the next targets of CyberMiles regarding adoption?
A: There is actually a main objective we are trying to achieve. Launched by a group of enthusiasts, we are revolutionizing e-commerce-a decentralized peer-to-peer marketplace. To make it simple, we are building the infrastructure of an e-commerce marketplace on our blockchain to enable its governance to be fully managed by its customers and community, who will decide what products can be listed and who can sell them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ask CyberMiles Question 5: Products sold need to have a stable price for buyers to measure the exact value. Does CyberMiles have a solution to stabilize prices for products sold despite the fluctuating CMT price?</title>
      <link>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190509-amaq5-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2019 17:05:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.cybermiles.io/post/20190509-amaq5-en/</guid>
      <description>Q: Products sold need to have a stable price for buyers to measure the exact value. Does CyberMiles have a solution to stabilize prices for products sold despite the fluctuating CMT price?
A: When we look at the past blockchain or decentralized ecommerce efforts, one of the biggest problem is Bitcoin&#39;s price fluctuation. And everyone who ever used bitcoin to buy stuff regret it. We remember the pizza story. I myself bought stuff with bitcoin.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>